Guide to the School of Art, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Art, Yale University, student records
1865-2004
RU 135
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
46.75
The records consist of student records of the Yale School of Art and its predecessors: School of Fine Arts, School of Architecture and Design, and School of Art and Architecture.
Yale University. School of Art
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 20-F (YRG 20-F), Student records of the Yale, School of Art.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is partially restricted. See inventory for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records of the Yale School of Art and its predecessors: School of Fine Arts, School of Architecture and Design, and School of Art and Architecture.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Art students; College students; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. School of Architecture and Design; Yale University. School of Art and Architecture; Yale University. School of Art; Yale University. School of Fine Arts
- Student records for the Classes of 1869-1985, Accession 1983-A-004
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 1-8 are open for research. Box 9 and the microfilm sub-series are partially restricted. See collection contents for details.
- Student transcripts [microfiche] for the Classes of 1986-2004, Accession 1987-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2080
  - Student transcripts [microfiche] for the Classes of 1986-2004, 1982-2004 (Box 1)
- Student records for the Classes of 1940-1949, Accession 1993-A-027 (Box 1–8)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
- School of the Fine Arts register, 1869-1915; Accession 1996-A-038
  The materials are open for research.
  - School of the Fine Arts register, 1869-1915 (Box 1)
- Students tuition record cards, address cards, enrollment cards, and notes recording payments and return address slips, 1870-1930; Accession 1996-A-070
  - Student enrollments cards, circa 1870- (Box 1)
  - Students of art school, 1905-1911 (Box 2)
  - Summer class enrollment, 1905-1906 (Box 2)
  - Evening class enrollment, 1905-1908 (Box 2)
  - Address information cards, 1923 (Box 2)
  - Student address cards, 1911-1917 (Box 2)
  - Student address cards, 1917-1930 (Box 3)
  - Address information cards, 1911-1914 (Box 3)
- Master of Fine Arts student records for the Classes of 1950-1959, Accession 2000-A-062
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2035
- Student records, 1960-1969; Accession 2010-A-046
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045